Guide to the Records of the New York University Men's and Women's Glee Clubs and Choral Arts Society RG 39.12
New York University Archives
- Series V: Photographs
  - Scrapbook, page 3 & 4: Rockefeller Center, Ed Sullivan Show, Time square, 1956, n.d (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook, page 5 & 6: E. Jon de Revere, misc., 1963, 1965, 1966 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 26)
  - Scrapbook, page 7 & 8: Mandeville, Jamaica, 1966 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook, page 9 & 10: Glee Club training camp, n.d. (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 28)
  - Scrapbook, page 11 & 12: Oratorio Society of New York, 10 May 1964 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 29)
  - Scrapbook, page 13 & 14: Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade, 1958 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 30)
  - Scrapbook, page 15 & 16: Puerto Rico, Jamaica, Montego Bay, Washington D.C. trips, 1965, 1966 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook, page 17 & 18: Williamsburg Garden Symposium Concert of Sacred Music, 23 Mar. 1965 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook, page 19 & 20: Varsity Quartet at Town Hall, 14 Oct. 1962 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 32)
  - Puerto Rico trip, 1963 (Box PHOTO 4, Folder 1)
  - Founders' Day Spring concert, 1964 (Box PHOTO 4, Folder 2)
  - Winter camp, 1964 (Box PHOTO 4, Folder 3)
  - 1964 Summer camp album (Box PHOTO 5, Folder 1)
  - The Goliards, n.d. (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 1)
  - The Goliards at Caneel Bay, Dec. 1964-Jan. 1965 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 2)
  - The Goliards at Caneel Bay, Dec. 1965 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 3)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, cover, n.d. (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 4)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 1 & 2, 1962, 1963 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 5)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 3 & 4, 1963, 1964 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 6)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 5 & 6, 1963, 1964 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 7)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 7 & 8, 1964 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 8)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 9 & 10, 1964, 1965 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 9)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 11 & 12, 1965 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 10)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 13 & 14, 1964, 1965 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 11)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 15 & 16, 1964, 1965 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 12)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 17 & 18, 1 May 1966 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 13)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 19 & 20, 1964, n.d. (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 14)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 21 & 22, 1966, n.d. (Box PHOTO 6, File 15)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 23 & 24, n.d. (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 15)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 25 & 26, 1967 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 16)
  - Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, page 27, 20 Mar. 1967 (Box PHOTO 6, Folder 17)
  - Town Hall album, before page 1, 11 Dec. 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 1)
  - Town Hall album, page 1, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 2)
  - Town Hall album, page 2, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 3)
  - Town Hall album, page 3, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 4)
  - Town Hall album, page 4, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 5)
  - Town Hall album, page 5, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 6)
  - Town Hall album, page 6, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 7)
  - Town Hall album, page 7, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 8)
  - Town Hall album, page 11, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 9)
  - Town Hall album, page 12, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 10)
  - Town Hall album, page 13, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 11)
  - Town Hall album, page 14, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 12)
  - Town Hall album, page 15, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 16)
  - Town Hall album, page 17, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 17)
  - Town Hall album, page 19, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 18)
  - Town Hall album, page 21, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 19)
  - Town Hall album, page 22, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 20)
  - Town Hall album, page 23, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 21)
  - Town Hall album, page 24, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 22)
  - Town Hall album, page 25, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 23)
  - Town Hall album, page 26, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 24)
  - Town Hall album, page 27, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 25)
  - Town Hall album, page 28, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 26)
  - Photo album M: 1968 Winter camp; 1967 Simmons College & Town Hall Weekends; 1968 Fifth Caribbean Tour, 1967, 1968 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 27)
  - Photo album M, page 2, n.d. (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 28)
  - Photo album M, page 3, n.d. (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 29)
  - Photo album M, page 4, n.d. (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 30)
  - Photo album M, page 5, 1965 (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 31)
  - Photo album M, page 6, n.d. (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 32)
  - Photo album M, page 7, n.d. (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 33)
  - Photo album M, page 8, n.d. (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 34)
  - Photo album M, page 9, n.d. (Box PHOTO 7, Folder 35)
  - Photo album M, page 10, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 1)
  - Photo album M, page 11, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 2)
  - Photo album M, page 12, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 3)
  - Photo album M, page 13, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 4)
  - Photo album M, page 14, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 5)
  - Photo album M, page 15, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 6)
  - Photo album M, page 16, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 7)
  - Photo album M, page 17, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 8)
  - Photo album M, page 18, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 9)
  - Photo album M, page 19, n.d. (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 10)
  - Virginia tour, Spring 1965 (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 11)
  - Michigan weekend, 29-31 Oct. 1965 (Box PHOTO 8, Folder 12)
- Series VI: Audiovisual recordings
  - The Goliard concert and demo tape, 1967 Nov. 18, 25 (Box AV 68, Reel 2626)
  - NYU Glee Club - Heights Concert, 1965 Dec. 11 (Box AV 68, Reel 2627)
  - NYU Glee Club - Heights Concert, 1966 Dec. (Box AV 68, Reel 2628)
- Series VII: Oversized material
  - Glee & Musical Club Members Portrait, 1921-1922 (Map-case 8, Drawer 7)
  - NYU Glee Club & Hall of Fame Singers Portrait, 12 Dec. 1942 (Map-case 8, Drawer 7)
  - Radcliffe Choral Society & NYU Glee Club Portrait, 11 Dec. 1953 (Map-case 8, Drawer 7)
  - Radcliffe Choral Society & NYU Glee Club Portrait, 11 Dec. 1953 (Map-case 8, Drawer 7)
  - NYU Glee Club Camp Portrait, 1963 (Map-case 8, Drawer 7)
  - NYU Glee Club Camp Portrait, 1966 (Map-case 8, Drawer 7)
  - Town Hall Concert with Simon's College Girls Photograph, 8 Dec. 1967 (Map-case 8, Drawer 7)